systemspeedup.com 2018-06-29

# Tuneup Pro - Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy. Feel safe and secure when you do business with us.   
  
General

Tuneup Pro. is strongly committed to protect your privacy and provide a safe online experience for all of our users and registered customers while offering the highest quality products and services to them. We may gather certain types of information about and from you to fulfill your request and serve your needs better, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions covering the collection and use of this information. This privacy statement discloses what information we may gather, how we may use it and how to correct or change it. Please read the "Privacy Policy" completely, as well as our 'Terms and Conditions' for use of information we may gather. Should you have any questions in this regard, feel free to contact us. 

What Information we may collect about you? 

Placing Orders  
Use of Programs 

You can visit our website, read products description and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. Since we provide our customers and newsletter subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service; we may request information about you under occasional circumstances. For your convenience and to serve you better, a customer account includes all the collected personal information we may have, however, you can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving newsletter and other information from us. 

We collect personally identifiable information; such as name, mailing address and e-mail address when you register to one of our products or place an order (see the section below for more information on placing order). Website visitors may register to receive our newsletter by submitting their name and e-mail address. 

Placing Orders 

If you wish to place an order for our products, you can generally enter the requisite details. In addition to the customary information that may be required to fill your order (full name, address, phone number, ship-to name and address etc.), collection of additional information such as your credit card number and credit card expiration date, is dependent on option of payment as we offer online and offline subscribers additional options such as check, money order and credit card order by fax or phone. 

Use of Programs 

In connection with the installation and use of Tuneup Pro applications we may collect certain information concerning the use of application or the services, including certain personal data and information about your PC. This may include, information about your installed software and hardware, your IP address, your operating system, about your version of installed Tuneup Pro's application including its product key, and about the use of individual functions of that Tuneup Pro's application including the relevant times. Some applications are dependant on use of WebServices for their functioning and they do send such relevant data with each use. 

Purpose of Data Collection  
Applications and Services can use the aforementioned information to send product recommendations, product updates and important customer service notifications directly to your computer. Furthermore, the data is used for the purposes of product and market analysis which enables us to improve individual products and the range of products and services. 

Sharing of Data with Third Party   
The aforementioned data may be shared with third party vendors and partners and it will be governed by their privacy policy, which will be provided to you when you accept any offer by them. 

Consent for the Collection, Storage, Use and Distribution of the Data  
You hereby agree to the collection and use of the such information or data by Tuneup Pro. 

What we may do with the Information we collect? 

How we may share Personal Information? 

Credit Card Companies 

Payment Gateways 

How do we use cookies? 

Links 

Changes to Privacy Policy 

Contact Information
